Round 1: General
1. What word is a cocktail, a common tool and a song by the White Stripes? (Screwdriver)
2. In which country do men use the most deodorant? (Japan)
3. Who is this? (Lance Armstrong)
4. Which country ruled the Philippines in 1900? (United States of America)
5. In this game of Catan, what are the odds of any player earning wood on a dice roll? (13/36)
6. Which of these words does not occur in the King James bible? Matrix, Beer or Rave? (Rave)
7. Which video game company makes the Streetfighter franchise? (Capcom)
8. What does HMJS stand for in Jamaican Navy ship names? (Her Majesty’s Jamaican Ship)
9. What’s the name of the Japanese Stock Index? (Nikkei) 
10 Which animal does not belong in this list? Cow, Goose, Boar or Doe? (Boar)

Round 2: Jeopardy! (teams choose a category in order of best team names)
1. Stars. It’s the measure of a star’s brightness. (What is magnitude?)
2. Tudors. Elisabeth the first called him dad. (Who is Henry the 8th?)
3. Lord of the Rings. Sauron lives in this evil land. (What is mordor?)
4. Pokémon. The items of human clothing worn by rebellious Squirtles in season 1. (What are sunglasses?)
5. 3-letter-words. Synonym of burrow, furrow and grub. (What is dig?)
6. National symbols. This is Canada’s national animal. (What is a beaver?) 
7. South America. A famous native civilization in the current day Andes. (Who are the inca’s?)
8. Dogs. This breed of dog is what Hachiko is. (What is Akita?).   
9. Cricket. This country is the current world champion of cricket. (What is England?)
10. Tim. The city where Tim studied Sociology. (What is Rotterdam?)
11. Code. 1010 in binary to decimal. (What is 10?)
12. War. Hemingway novel about desertion. (What is a Farewell to Arms?) 
13. Beer. Country of origin of beer brand Efes. (What is Turkey?) 
14. Corona. This is the word found under “Corona” on their beer bottles. (What is Extra?)
15. Flags. Number of colours in the flag of Cuba. (What is 3?)
16. Food. This classic English dish is an anagram of “hot toe inhaled”. (What is toad in the hole?)

Round 3: Music
1. What is the name of this song? (Madonna - Frozen, Frozen)
2. What is the next line of the song? (Beatles - Here There and Everywhere, Running my hands through her hair)
3. Who is the artist? (The Weeknd - Blinding Lights, The Weeknd)
4. Of which country is this the national anthem? (Kimi Ga Yo - Japan, Japan)
5. Who is the artist? (Wu-tang Clan - C.R.E.A.M, Wu Tang Clan)
6. What is the artist’s real surname? (David Bowie - Modern Love, Jones)
7. What is the name of this song? (U2 - Kite, Kite)
8. Of which song is this a cover? (Master of Puppets Flute Cover, Metallica - Master of Puppets) 
9. Who is this artist? (Ska-p - Mis Colegas, Ska-p)
10. What is the next line in the song? (Radiohead - Paranoid Android, You will be first against the wall)

Round 4: TV and Movies
1. What is this 2002 show called? (The Wire)
2. Who won the oscar for best actress in 2020? (Renée Zellweger)
3. What will happen next? (A jet engine will come crashing through the roof)
4. Who directed Skyfall? (Sam Mendes)
5. Which TV show had this intro tune? (Star Trek)
6. From which movie is the line: I’ll have what she’s having? (When Harry met Sally)
7. Who survives the movie the longest? (dark-haired girl)
8. In which BBC2 game show are the contestants trying to score the least possible points with their answers? (Pointless)
9. What happens next? (The monkey says “no”)
10. Which movie does this poster depict? (The Help)

Round 5: Places
1. Where am I? (Czech Republic)
2. Where am I? (Ireland)
3. Where am I? (Croatia)
4. Where am I? (France)
5. Where am I? (Australia)
6. Where am I? (Chile)
7. Where am I? (The Netherlands)
8. Where am I? (Germany)
9. Where am I? (Spain)
10. Where am I? (China)









